fire the Secretary of Veterans Affairs response to the outrage this evening and would a man says he resigned allegations that bats have died because of substandard medical care
消防退伍军人事务部长的回应愤怒今天晚上会和一个男人说，他辞职是因为不合格医疗的指控，蝙蝠死亡
Tara sue kidnapped those teenage girls in Nigeria as worldwide condemnation gross a question of excessive force
塔拉起诉绑架那些十几岁的女孩在尼日利亚为全世界的谴责总值用力过度问题
rise up an American city where the police department in suspected of killing civilians at alarming rate and high anxiety if you can stand it
站起来的美国城市，警察部门在涉嫌以惊人的速度和高焦虑杀害平民，如果你能忍受
94 stories about Chicago the lean out over the city of big shoulders Nightly News begins now
94故事有关芝加哥的探出整个城市的大肩膀的晚间新闻现在开始
this is NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams
这是NBC晚间新闻与布赖恩·威廉斯
good evening they have all volunteered for duty and serve their nation with distinction they have sacrificed their families to do the same domestically in overseas and when they come home to the thanks of a grateful nation they have every right to expect at a grateful nation will take care of them
晚上好，他们都自愿参加义务和服务于他们的国家相区别，他们都牺牲了自己的家庭，在国内国外做同样的，当他们回家感恩的民族，他们有权利期望在感恩的民族权利的感谢会照顾他们
but as we learn more about a non folding healthcare scandal in the Veterans Administration it's now clear that's not happening in all cases and some of our vets have been ignored neglected under treated and mistreated with sometimes fatal consequences
但随着我们更多地了解在退伍军人管理局的非折叠的医疗丑闻，这是现在很清楚，没有发生在所有情况下，有些我们的兽医都被忽略了下处理被忽视和虐待与有时甚至是致命的后果
tonight the man in charge of the VA a former 4 star general decorated combat veteran himself
今晚的负责人，弗吉尼亚州的前四星级普通装饰作战退伍军人自己
is trying to fix this and hang onto is job today he sat down with our Pentagon correspondent Jim miklaszewski who starts off tonight
正试图解决这一问题，并挂到是今天的​​工作，他坐下来与我们的五角大楼的记者吉姆miklaszewski今晚谁开始起飞
even for the troubled Department of Veterans Affairs it's a shocking scandal die while waiting for medical care at the VA hospital in Phoenix
即使是退伍军人事务部陷入困境这是一个令人震惊的丑闻模具在等待医疗在VA医院在凤凰城
I am hungry
我想饿
television interview pa Secretary Eric Shinseki told in DC news that he was surprised at the allegations what promised a full investigation
电视采访PA秘书辛塞奇告诉记者，在直流消息，他惊讶于这些指控有什么承诺全面调查
are you willing is the Secretary of Veterans Affairs to accept full responsibility
你是否愿意为退伍军人事务司承担全部责任
I am Vanessa reason the ideal standard during the investigation
我是凡妮莎原因在调查过程中的理想标准
Hospital whistleblowers claim the internet for to improve their performance record administrators 1001 official
医院告密者声称互联网进行，以改善他们的表现记录管理员1001官方
not to be reported if they die their names with disappear 10 to the 18 months of combating the system to get an appointment
如果他们死了自己的名字与消失10至18个月打击系统，以获得预约不予以报道
you have to break through or basically do a full frontal assault in order to get an appointment
你必须突破或基本做了充分的正面进攻，以获得一个约会
veterans groups of exploded an outrage the American Legion has the resignation
退伍军人团体爆炸太可恶了美国退伍军人协会有辞职
these are just unacceptable things that have come about thats that let us do this decision
这些都只是已经到来，那是让我们做这个决定无法接受的事情
what you did today is going nowhere they want you to resign or be fired
你做了什么今天是无处可去，他们要你辞职或者被解雇
will you resign I would say I serve at the pleasure of the President
你会辞职，我会说我在担任总统的乐趣
Veterans of America says the Veterans Administration Lex leadership accountability and curry
美国退伍军人说，退伍军人管理局莱克斯领导责任制和咖喱
unfortunately is quickly becoming a punchline in this country
不幸的是正迅速成为一个点睛之笔，在这个国家
bad for v8 it bad for a better internet bad for America
祈求V8它要求一个更好的互联网祈求美国
it gets worse as investigators closed and I know it Phoenix VA hospital
它变得更糟，因为调查结束，我知道这凤凰VA医院
Hospital officials order the records destroyed Paris
医院官员下令销毁记录巴黎
David it was important for an investigation
大卫是一个重要的调查
have it significant
有它显著
alter an insect a scandalous spreading new allegations of falsified records have crept up at VA hospitals in Austin San Antonio and Fort Collins Colorado 109 veteran claims the VA has lost its humanity
改变昆虫的伪造记录的丑闻传播新的指控不断攀升，在VA医院在奥斯汀的圣安东尼奥和科罗拉多州柯林斯堡109老兵声称，弗吉尼亚州已经失去了它的人性
clear people we bleed we cry we need the services and I don't want them to forget it
清晰的人，我们流血，我们哭了，我们需要的服务，我不希望他们忘记它
Shinseki is a graduate of West Point he was wounded in Vietnam and rose to the level of general in army chief of staff completely understand
新关是西点军校的毕业生，他被打伤在越南和上升到一般水平，陆军参谋长完全理解
why there is at level of outrage right now awesome kind of them off around my self
为什么会出现在愤怒的层面，现在真棒样的人在我的自我关闭
reporters who is a pentagon a foot lotions for years first does a general Dennis via a secretary and it seems today that even Shinseki Mary live
记者谁是五边形足乳液多年来第一次做了一般的丹尼斯通过秘书，今天似乎连新关玛丽直播
that the initial response is by the VA to many of these scandals will still not satisfied many of those veterans wine
，最初的反应是由弗吉尼亚州许多这些丑闻仍不会满足其中的许多老兵酒
reporting today from the Pentagon Jim Finks the United States is gearing up for an urgent mission in Nigeria tonight to provide military and other support
从五角大楼吉姆芬克斯美国今天的报告是摩拳擦掌，为在尼日利亚今晚一项紧急任务，提供军事和其他支持
the help find and secure the release of hundreds of kidnapped schoolgirls ass outrage grows in this country in around the world the terrorists are showing no signs down in fact quite the contrary we get the very latest from Archie foreign affairs correspondent Andrea Mitchell
帮助查找和预定数百绑架女学生的屁股释放愤怒生长在这个国家在世界各地的恐怖分子都没有显示出下降的迹象，其实恰恰相反，我们得到阿奇外交事务记者安德里亚·米切尔的最新
were the three weeks after the terrorist kidnapping the protests in Nigeria's capital earn a quieter put in the shadows of the burned out school 500 miles from the capital of Israel
被三个星期恐怖绑架后，在尼日利亚首都的抗议活动赢得一个安静的摆在被烧毁的学校从以色列的首都500英里阴影
some of the girls family hide at night and red of Boca Hurom returning protected they say by only a dozen police a community leader speaking to parents on the phone describes one father's agony not knowing his daughters fake
一些女孩的家庭隐藏在夜间的博卡Hurom返回保护和红色的，他们说只有十几个警察作为社会的领袖说话的父母在电话中描述了一个父亲的痛苦，不知道他的女儿假
it is better did you know that the cell is it better He said then imagining her raped and sold as a sex slave Fairfield or justified not far away another attack earlier this week hundreds possibly killed
最好是你知道细胞是更好，他说，然后想象她强奸并卖为性奴隶的Fairfield还是有道理不远处的另一次攻击这个星期早些时候数百个可能被杀害
national community finally slowly awakening
全国社区终于慢慢觉醒
I'm the father of two young daughters who's in every father and mother in this land or in the world this is an actual pure evil
我的两个年幼的女儿的父亲是谁在每一位父亲和母亲在这片土地上，还是在世界，这是一个实际的纯粹的邪恶
Michelle Obama Tonight tweeting our prayers are with a missing Nigerian girls and their families its time do you hashtag bring back or girls speaking out today Malala yousafzai the Pakistani teen savagely shot by the Taliban for attending school
米歇尔·奥巴马今晚啁啾我们的祈祷与缺失尼日利亚女孩及其家人的时候，你的hashtag带回或女孩今天讲出来马拉拉yousafzai巴基斯坦少年被塔利班枪杀野蛮上学
now an icon for girls education around the world with NBC's bill Neely
现在对于全世界与NBC的法案尼利各地女童教育的图标
Great Britain France the US are now Mobilising the US will likely send surveillance drones FBI assistance and intelligence help with fewer than 10 more uniform military advisors and no helicopters as of now this is not a search and rescue mission
英国法国美国正动员美国可能会少于10更均匀军事顾问，没有直升机送侦察机协助美国联邦调查局和情报的帮助，现在这不是一个搜索和救援任务
Nigeria heaven help us against Boko Haran the extremist Islamic movement terrorizing NE Nigeria Hillary Clinton today Boca Hurom is abominable for Nigeria's government is not without blame
尼日利亚天堂帮助我们对博科哈兰的极端伊斯兰运动今天恐吓尼日利亚东北希拉里·克林顿博卡Hurom恶劣尼日利亚政府也不是没有怪
Government of Nigeria has been in my view someone derelect and its responsibility for protecting boys and girls men and women in northern Nigeria over the last years
尼日利亚政府已经在我看来有人derelect及其责任在过去几年保护男孩和女孩男性和女性在尼日利亚北部
tonight in a striking contrast Nigeria's capital is hosting the World Economic Forum the world's wealth is corporate leaders
今晚在了鲜明的对比尼日利亚的首都将举办世界经济论坛的世界财富是企业领袖
possibly diverting security forces that could otherwise be searching for the missing girls
可能分流安全部队，否则可能会寻找失踪女孩
Michelin or Washington newsroom tonight Andrea Sykes
米其林或华盛顿编辑部今晚安德烈赛克斯
we turn out of the crisis in Ukraine and a new claim by a flat Amir Putin's that he has now moved tens of thousands of his Russian troops away from the
我们把走出危机在乌克兰和一台阿米尔普京的一个新的说法，他现在已经搬到了俄罗斯军队数万远离的
clear if that is actually happened Archie foreign correspondent Richard Engel following it all from Donetsk in the eastern part of the country Richard good evening
清楚，如果这是实际发生的阿奇外国记者理查德·恩格尔下面的这一切从顿涅茨克在全国理查德晚上好东部
good evening Brian if it were true he would be a major development in the escalate the crisis hear the problem is according to NATO official US military officials in US intelligence officials it is it true that looking at the satellites
晚上好布莱恩，如果它是真实的，他将在减缓危机听到这个问题的一个主要的发展是按照北约官员美国军方官员在美国情报官员是真的，看着卫星
In N Out singing any significant change in Russian troop movements so why make the claim Latimer Putin today made many surprising statement he called on Russian separatist here in eastern Ukraine to postpone a referendum on independence of events leading to hold
在正出在唱俄罗斯调兵任何显著改变，为什么使索赔拉蒂默普京今天提出了很多令人惊讶的声明，他呼吁俄罗斯分裂在这里乌克兰东部推迟对导致事件举行独立公投
you said he wants an end to this crisis
你说，他希望结束这场危机
it seems that couldn't run a present himself as a peacemaker not aggressive it could be a tactic
似乎不能运行一个把自己打扮成一个和事佬不冒进它可能是一种策略
Richard Engel in Donetsk Ukraine forest and I Richardson TX a big part of this country is dealing with an early heatwave tonight
理查德·恩格尔在乌克兰顿涅茨克林和我德克萨斯州理查森这个国家的很大一部分是今晚对付早期热浪
with records being broken and farmers now facing a tough time just as they are growing season in many cases just now gets underway NBC's Janet shamlian covering for us in Clearwater Kansas tonight
有纪录被打破，农民正面临着一个艰难的时间，就像他们在许多情况下，生长季节刚才开杆NBC的珍妮特shamlian在堪萨斯州克利尔沃特覆盖为我们今晚
this field should be full of young porn right now that they have not be planted because it's simply to drive there hoping for a significant rain but they're not going to get it
这个字段应该是充满了年轻的色情的，现在，他们还没有被种植，因为它只是推动有希望的一个显著的雨，但他们不会得到它
biggest crop in Kansas all over the states
各地州堪萨斯州最大的作物
this is probably one of the worst cross at the states that I've ever seen in my 52 years
这可能是最糟糕的交叉点上的状态，我已经见过我的52年1
John Jenkinson is an egg special if your family is that in Farmington generation and he knows it harvest has been hard hit just by looking at it this week should be
约翰·詹金森是一个特殊的鸡蛋，如果你的家庭是，在法明顿一代，他知道它已收割刚刚在这个星期看它沉重打击应该是
waste Island on both of us that's less than half of work today and we're going ham
浪费岛我俩这不到一半的工作，今天我们要去火腿
more than less of a half of a cup
不止少了一个杯子的一半
what should have Kansas is locked in a heatwave August temperatures in early May
什么应该是堪萨斯州在五月初锁定在了八月的热浪温度
and could it be Wichita sauce no just 3 weeks ago today is in the 90 blanketing the southern plains
而不可能是威奇托酱无短短3个星期前的今天是在90笼罩南部平原
Wichita hit 95 today a record Kansas City with 15 degrees above normal 887 n in Concordia Kansas 98 degrees break in a 127 year old record
威奇托打到95日的纪录堪萨斯城有高于正常887 n以康科迪亚堪萨斯州15度98度127岁破纪录
what you see on this map is where we expect temperatures to be the cooler or hotter than they normally would be where the drought is so bad temperature is it going to be hot because the atmosphere just going to continue to bake we expected route to build even more so in the planes as we go to the summer months
你在这张地图看到什么是我们预期的温度是冷或热比他们通常会到什么地方干旱是如此糟糕温度也将成为热点，因为大气中只是要继续烘烤我们的预期路线，甚至建更多的是在飞机，因为我们去的夏季
in Oklahoma is could be another 1935 Dust Bowl says the USDA 3904 condition tour last week of farms in Kansas forecast the weakest cropping 18 years in the top US wheat producing state
在俄克拉何马可能是另一个1935年沙尘暴农场上周表示，美国农业部3904巡演条件在堪萨斯预测最弱种植18年美国顶级的小麦生产州
and you can see how dry and windy it is here be on the cross public utilities in Wichita Lone water uses of 25% last week due to the heat
你可以看到如何干燥多风它在这里是在上上周的25％威奇托龙水利用交叉公用事业由于热
Janet shamlian live in Clearwater Kansas Forest Hill LIJ
珍妮特shamlian住在堪萨斯州克利尔沃特森林山LIJ
thanks one more noght on all the severe weather we've been seeing President Obama was in Arkansas today taking look at the destruction from the tornadoes in 10 days ago now feeling 1501 hard hat area the president 7 something like this happens it happens to all of us
感谢所有的恶劣天气，我们已经看到美国总统奥巴马多一个noght在阿肯色州今天服用看看的破坏从10天前感觉现在1501安全帽区总裁7这样的事情发生了它发生在所有的龙卷风我们
you did that by way of pledging the federal government will be there until these communities are all rebuilt
你是通过质押的方式，联邦政府将在那里，直到这些社区都是重建
teams of federal agents found out across the country today in a widening crackdown now on the growing black market for synthetic drugs DEA said its agents arrested
联邦特工队今天发现了在全国范围内现在是扩大打击日益增长的黑市上用​​作合成药物的DEA表示，其特工逮捕
150 people serve 200 warrants sees 20 million dollars in cash and assets drugs including synthetic marijuana and bass artists
150人服务于200份认股权证认为2000万美元的现金和资产的药物，包括合成大麻和低音艺术家
yesterday was primary day in a few states and won election results still a cliffhanger featuring a well-known Canada and would be member of Congress former American Idol star Clay Aiken is in a slim lead in the primary for a house in North Carolina 2nd district
昨天是小学一天在几个国家，并赢得选举结果仍是一个悬念设有一个著名的加拿大和美国国会会成员前美国偶像明星粘土艾肯是在微弱的领先优势在主的房子在北卡罗莱纳州第二区
Tara Simon outstanding balance it still hasn't been called when are the Democratic primary phases in uphill fight against the Republican and November there's a full wrap up a primary results in the politics section of our website
塔拉西蒙余额仍然没有被调用的时候都在反对共和，十一月上坡斗争民主党初选阶段有一个全包裹在我们网站的政治部分的主要结果
Castle Knights Edison's rising
城堡骑士爱迪生的崛起
against a police department in charge of excessive force following is a series of shootings captured on video and later the highest lookout
对下列警察部门负责过度用力是一系列枪击事件的录像，后来最高的了望
kind in all the land leaning out over Chicago a first look tonight at the view from above that won't be forever
那种在所有的土地靠在了超过芝加哥今晚从以上观点先看看会不会是永远
we are back with a report about a city on the edge of the use of excessive force often recorded on video the police in Albuquerque New Mexico
我们回来了，大约一个城市的过度使用武力往往录像记录，警方在阿尔伯克基新墨西哥州的边缘报告
remanded by the US Department of Justice protesters disrupted the City Council meeting earlier this week and they plan to do it again tomorrow night
由司法部，美国能源部还押示威者扰乱了市议会会议本星期早些时候，他们打算再这样做，明天夜间
to make sure their message gets heard we get our report tonight from our justice correspondent Pete Williams
以确保他们的消息被听到我们得到我们从我们的正义的记者皮特·威廉斯今晚报告
seems like this if spark outrage over the tactics of Albuquerque Police homeless man carrying small knives is accused of illegally camping in mid March in order to surrender a fire a stun grenade
似乎是这个，如果火花愤慨的阿尔伯克基警方无家可归的男子携带小刀具的战术被指控非法露营在三月中旬才能交出失火的眩晕手榴弹
find a open fire killing ham in the past 4 years police in Albuquerque have sharp 39 people killing 26
找到一个开放式壁炉杀人火腿在过去的4年警方在阿尔伯克基已经尖锐39人杀26
part of a pattern the Justice Department's is it using excessive force unconstitutional on Monday protesters disrupted the meaning of the City Council using officials of failing to doing nothing response
的司法部正在使用过度武力违宪周一抗议者它一个模式的一部分扰乱了市议会的意思用失败的官员无所事事响应
the meeting is rescheduled for tomorrow but the protester say they'll be back
该会议改在明天，但示威者说，他们会回来的
should demonstrate the level of frustration frustration among the people that live in Albuquerque with fear
应表现出无奈的无奈，生活在阿尔伯克基的恐惧在人民群众中的水平
blistering report last month the Justice Department police in Albuquerque are too quick to use deadly force against people who posed only a minimal use inappropriate for people who are
上个月起泡报告司法部警察在阿尔伯克基过于快速使用致命武力对付谁提出的只是一个极小的使用不当人的人谁是
Sibley resisting or non threatening and use more force than needed in handling people with mental illnesses
西布利抗拒或不威胁和使用比需要更多的力量在处理人与精神疾病
what's roughly 1000 officers Albuquerque Police Department is New Mexico's largest now police there find a community skeptical of ever use of force last weekend police released only a short video clip after officers head shot and killed a 50-year-old Air Force veteran Armand Martin
什么是大约1000官员阿尔伯克基警察局是新墨西哥州最大的现在警方有找到一个怀疑曾经使用武力的社会人员头部开枪打死一名50岁的空军老将阿尔芒·马丁之后发布仅一个短片的最后一个周末警察
ELISA hip thrusting his wife and her two children with a gun then ran out shooting investigation this video showed him with a gun inside
酶联免疫吸附臀推他的妻子和她的两个孩子带了一把枪，然后跑了出去调查拍摄这段视频显示了他的枪里面
Albuquerque says he will do more to improve police training oversight City to face federal criticism of excessive force as the Obama administration more aggressively polices the police
阿尔布开克说，他将更加努力提高警察培训监督城市面临的过猛，奥巴马政府联邦的批评更积极政策的警察
Justice Department
司法部
will take a quick break here we're back in the moment with the star of the sports world proving why he's the most valuable
将采取快速突破这里我们回到当下与体育界的证明为什么他是最有价值的明星
there's space news tonight as we repeatedly there a host of websites and apps that let you grab the kids and let you know when you can go outside and watch the International Space Station
还有空间消息今晚我们反复有许多网站，让你抢孩子，让你知道当你可以到外面去，看着国际空间站应用
flyover where you live shining brightly moving fast against the night sky well now as of today we can see what we look like from up there in real time
天桥你住在哪里灿烂地照耀着快速移动对夜空现在好了今天，我们可以看到我们的样子从那里实时
there are over 200 miles of moving at seventeen thousand miles an hour now there live streaming at all in high definition you'll see a sunrise and a sunset every 90 minutes there's a link to it on our website
有超过200浬，17000英里一个小时移动现在还有现场直播在所有的高清晰度，你会看到一个日出和日落每90分钟有我们的网站上链接到它的
while we have a more extensive report on this
虽然我们对此有更广泛的报告
next door in the days to come we wanna do alert you to a Nazy ating sight in one of the most beautiful places most breathtaking places in our country someone sadly is poaching the giant redwoods in California
在未来的日子里，我们想做的事提醒您到Nazy ATING视线在我国有人黯然被偷猎的巨型红杉在加州最美丽的地方最激动人心的地方之一隔壁
cutting into them with chainsaws hacking into them for the burl sections of the wood the Elk Groce that are similar to large barnacles they are Prize for their wood grain patterns
切成他们用电锯黑客进入他们的木材麋鹿Groce的瘤节类似于大藤壶它们奖为他们的木纹图案
it's believed some of the poachers are meth addicts the wood can sell for thousands of dollars are national treasures have paid a high price
它认为一些偷猎者是甲基成瘾木材能卖到几千块钱是国宝付出了高昂的代价
these are thousand year old trees already one has been killed and many of them have been permanently harmed
这些都是千年古树已经人被打死，其中许多已被永久伤害
after all the negative attention directed toward the NBA won t motor in particular thankfully we got to see just yesterday the very best of the NBA
后指向了NBA那些负面的眼光赢得吨尤其是电机谢天谢地，我们终于看到就在昨天最优秀的NBA
4 time scoring champion Kevin Durant of the Oklahoma City Thunder was accepting the most valuable player award when he decided to dedicate 300 was mother who was there at the ceremony
俄克拉何马城雷霆4得分王杜兰特被接受最有价值球员奖时，他决定奉献300是母亲谁在那里在仪式上
Wanda Pratt was a single mother of two boys by the age of 21 Durant made it clear without her he wouldn't be where is today
万达普拉特是由两个男生21杜兰特岁的单身母亲说清楚没有她，他就不会是今天在哪里
Jet magazine is ending publication of its print edition right on the heels of Ladies Home Journal doing the same jet is switching to the web after 63 years in print
喷气杂志右侧结束对妇女家庭杂志的出版高跟鞋其印刷版的做同样的射流后，63岁的打印切换到Web
these days jet is there a manga scenes and African American leadership and well there slogan used to be if it is in NJ that didn't happen these days ebony enjoys a huge lead in circulation
这些天飞机是有一个漫画场景和非洲裔美国人的领导能力和良好有使用的口号是，如果它是在新泽西州没有发生这些天乌木享有巨大的领先优势在流通
our company made news today the International Olympic Committee as a grade one almost 8 billion dollar deal with NBC for broadcast rights to the Olympics through the year 2032 that's a long time in the deal includes the rights to games in cities that have yet to be selective
本公司生产的消息，今天国际奥委会作为一个一年级近8十亿美元的交易与NBC的转播权的奥运会通过2032年那是一个很长的时间在处理包含的权利，这还有待选择性的在城市的游戏
The Last Summer Games in London most watched on US television history vioc did not put the rice out for business time instead approach the network about an extension when we come back here tonight a spectacular view from above and has USC
去年夏天伦敦奥运会最受瞩目的美国电视史上VIOC没把饭出来的业务时间，而不是接近约一个扩展的网络，当我们回到这里，今晚从上面的壮丽景色，并拥有南加州大学
as we say not forever
当我们说永远不
finally here tonight fair warning hang on to something as we take you high above Chicago for a new attraction opening this weekend decidedly not for those who fear great heights it is for those with strong stomachs love a great deal of red grapes
终于来了，今晚公平的警告挂的东西，因为我们带你高高在上芝加哥的一个新景点开幕本周末决然不是为那些谁害怕高处它是为那些具有强烈的胃爱了大量的红葡萄
we get a preview tonight from our man in Chicago NBC is Kevin Tibbles
我们从男性在芝加哥NBC得到一个预览今晚是凯文Tibbles
you've got a crick in your neck to see Chicago's newest attraction travel straight up 1030 to the 94 floor of the John Hancock Center
你已经有了一个克里克在你的脖子，看看芝加哥的最新景点旅游直上1030到94楼的约翰汉考克中心
like to see someone else text first
这里首先要看到别人的文字
form for up to 8 people
形成了多达8人
juicers
榨汁机
with spectacular views about to 50 miles
与即将50英里壮观景色
project not literally but yes
项目不是真的，但肯定
pronto help build
弹指一挥间，帮助建立
using tempered glass
使用强化玻璃
after all this is the Windy City
毕竟这是风城
what's a heaven for you I love big fan of hives
什么是老天爷给你的我爱荨麻疹的忠实粉丝
Planet on terra firma down below overwhelm you come right out
地球上的陆地向下跌破压倒你来的权利，
is it comes out and you go
是它出来和你走
tilting where no one has tilted before
倾斜在那里没有人前倾斜
factor pairs
因素对
heart stopping views of the Second City
市二中的心脏停止跳动的意见
safely from the other side of the glass Kevin Tibbles NBC News Chicago
安全地从玻璃凯文Tibbles NBC新闻芝加哥的另一面
joy the view what could go wrong that's our broadcast on a Wednesday night thank you for being here with us on Brian Williams wear for a cell to see you right back here tomorrow evening good
欢乐的观点有什么可以去错了这是我们的广播在周三晚上谢谢你能在这里和我们的布赖恩·威廉斯穿了一个单元格来查看你的右后卫在这里明天晚上好